Bridge Line Historical Society; Collection mss129
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Maps, Blueprints, and Drawings, 1870-2004; 2; 613 items
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Proposed Standard Combination Tool House and Sectionmen, Undated (Map-tube 390)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000516-BLA000518
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Proposed Standard Tool House Sectionmen, Undated (Map-tube 289)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001136
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Proposed Standard Tool House Sectionmen, Undated (Map-tube 331)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001137
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Proposed Standard Tool House Sectionmen, Undated (Map-tube 365)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001138
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Proposed Standard Tool House Sectionmen, Undated (Map-tube 378)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001139
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Railroad Department for All Divisions Detour Map (Reproduction of 1908 Map), Undated (Map-tube 397)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000177; Other Identification Number: 41-20499
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Round House Chimney Blueprint in Green Island, NY (Reproduction of 1900 Map), Undated (Map-tube 240)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000503-BLA000503A
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Sanitary Closet at Wadhams Mills (Reproduction of 1902 Map), Undated (Map-tube 278)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001100; Other Identification Number: 611-7107
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Saratoga Division, Classification of Yard Tracks in Colonie (Reproduction of 1923 Map), Undated (Map-tube 260)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001030
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Saratoga Division, Proposed Camp Cars for Extra Track Gangs (Reproduction of 1922 Map), Undated (Map-tube 258)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001134
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Saratoga Division, Proposed New Engine Shelter in Fort Edward, NY (Reproduction of 1909 Map), Undated (Map-tube 231)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000508A-BLA000508C; Other Identification Number: 518-20608
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Saratoga Division, Scale Drawings for Sand House in Saratoga, NY (Reproduction of 1904 Map), Undated (Map-tube 242)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000522; Other Identification Number: 56-4725
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Saratoga Division, Scale Drawings for Sand House in Saratoga, NY (Reproduction of 1904 Map), Undated (Map-tube 450)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000522A
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Saratoga Division; Addition to Road House in Saratoga, NY (Reproduction of 1903 Map), Undated (Map-tube 419)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001168
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Saratoga Division; Additions to Round House in Saratoga, NY (Reproduction of 1904 Map), Undated (Map-tube 222)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000501A-BLA000501B
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Saratoga Division; Adirondack Division, Yard Map of North Creek, NY (Reproduction of 1914 Map), Undated (Map-tube 425)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001364
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Saratoga Division; Classification of Yard Tracks in Colonie (Reproduction of 1923 Map), Undated (Map-tube 313)
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Saratoga Division; Engine House Ash Pit, Coaling Platform and Track Improvements in Fort Edward, NY (Reproduction of 1912 Map), Undated (Map-tube 405)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001374
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Saratoga Division; Green Island Branch, Development Map No. 1, Freight House and Yard T racks in Green Island, NY (Reproduction of 1912 Map), Undated (Map-tube 417)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001362; Other Identification Number: 57-23239
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Saratoga Division; Green Island Branch, Development Map No. 1, Freight House and Yard T racks in Green Island, NY (Reproduction of 1912 Map), Undated (Map-tube 418)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001375; Other Identification Number: 57-23418
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Saratoga Division; Lake George Branch, Grounds Adjacent to Fort William Henry Hotel and D&H Station, Showing Buildings, Roadways, Paths and Underground Structures, Pipelines, Etc. (Reproduction of 1915 Map), Undated (Map-tube 392)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001285; Other Identification Number: 810-26642
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Saratoga Division; New Engine Coaling Plant in Saratoga, NY (Reproduction of 1912 Map), Undated (Map-tube 426)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001373
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Saratoga Division; Plan for Proposed Waiting Room to be Located at West End of Bridge No. 11 in Green Island New York (Reproduction of 1908 Map), Map Number 465, Undated (Flat-file 1)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001278
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Saratoga Division; Scale Drawings for Sandhouse in Saratoga, NY (Reproduction of 1904 Map), Map Number 485, Undated (Flat-file 2)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000522
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Saratoga Division; Washington Bridge Valuation Section 9-E, Yard Map of Greenwich Junction (Reproduction of 1934 Map), Undated (Map-tube 218)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001324; Other Identification Number: 810-36138
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Sketch Showing Existing Railroad's Facilities at and in the Vicinity of Albany, NY (Reproduction of 1928 Map), Undated (Map-tube 420)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000035
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Standard Ballast Template (Reproduction of 1917 Map), Undated (Map-tube 363)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000992; Other Identification Number: 21-250
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Standard Double Toolhouse, 1922 (Map-tube 352)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001140
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Standard Rail Rack (Reproduction of 1917 Map), Undated (Map-tube 354)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001023; Other Identification Number: 21-252
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Standard Road Crossings (Reproduction of 1917 Map), Undated (Map-tube 326)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001009
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Standard Station Sign "Cohoes" (Reproduction of 1926 Map), Undated (Map-tube 285)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000848
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Steel Underframe of Box Car, Undated (Map-tube 459)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000497
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division Design for Roof Trusses in Old Machine Shop [Should be Shop 7 Car Repair] (Reproduction of 1904 Map), Undated (Map-tube 238)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000476
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division Roundhouse Heating System in Oneonta Blueprint (Reproduction of 1920 Map), Undated (Map-tube 215)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000462
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division Schoharie Junction, Proposed Changes to Wye (Reproduction of 1918 Map), Undated (Map-tube 235)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000459
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division Valuation Section 4, Vision Survey of Rose Avenue in Oneonta, NY (Reproduction of 1926 Map), Undated (Map-tube 233)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000473
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division Valuation Section 4, Washroom Facilities and Restroom Roundhouse in Oneonta, NY (Reproduction of 1927 Map), Undated (Map-tube 237)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000466
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division Valuation Section 4; General Layout of Piping at Round House in Oneonta, NY Blueprint (Reproduction of 1920 Map), Undated (Map-tube 217)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000461
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division Valuation Section 4; Location of Shower Room at Roadhouse in Oneonta, NY, 1937 (Map-tube 229)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000465
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division, Location of Derrick in Colliers, NY (Reproduction of 1924 Map), Undated (Map-tube 277)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001120
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division, Location of Derrick in Maryland, NY (Reproduction of 1925 Map), Undated (Map-tube 274)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001125
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division, Plan Showing Location of Tracks and Tell-Tales Near New Coal Pockets at Delanson, NY (Reproduction of 1907 Map), Undated (Map-tube 261)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000523
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division, Proposed Ditching West of Mains 0.34 Mile South of Barnerville, NY (Reproduction of 1925 Map), Undated (Map-tube 268)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000509
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Additions to Express Building at Wells Bridge to Serve as Car Repair Building at Glens Bridge, NY (Reproduction of 1928), Undated (Map-tube 347)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001143
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Bridge 50 Plan No. 597, Two Spans, Single Track, Deck, Plate Girder, Undated (Map-tube 284)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001016
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Bridge 78.92 (Old 566) (Reproduction of 1915 Map), Undated (Map-tube 329)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001005
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Bridge No. 50 Plan for Second Track, Undated (Map-tube 314)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001015
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Cattle Pass at Station 3520+30 (Reproduction of 1917 Map), Undated (Map-tube 310)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001158
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Cattle Pass at Station 3789+95, Undated (Map-tube 360)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000996
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Changes to Masonry of Bridge 54 (Reproduction of 1912 Map), Undated (Map-tube 312)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001000
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Changes to Masonry South Abutment of Bridge 54 (Reproduction of 1913 Map), Undated (Map-tube 371)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001002
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Clearances at Davenport Branch Bride Crossing Mains at Cooperstown Junction, NY (Reproduction of 1925 Map), Undated (Map-tube 376)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001026
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Comparative Statement of Estimates of Various Lines from Binghamton to Belden (Reproduction of 1912 Map), Undated (Map-tube 388)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001164-BLA001166
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Detail of Deck Bridge No. 70.41 (Reproduction of 1928 Map), Undated (Map-tube 357)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001022
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Detail of Deck Bridge No. 76.28 (Reproduction of 1926 Map), Undated (Map-tube 346)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000998
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Detail of Deck to Bridge No. 78.92 (Reproduction of 1926), Undated (Map-tube 386)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001007
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Detail of S.B. Deck Bridge 66.31 (Reproduction of 1936 Map), Undated (Map-tube 332)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000976
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Details of Deck Bridge 74.15 (Reproduction of 1932 Map), Undated (Map-tube 323)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001102; Other Identification Number: 52-9
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Details of Deck, S.B.M. Bridge 64.02 (Reproduction of 1932), Undated (Map-tube 322)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001154
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Double Track Stone Ballast Section, 1921 (Map-tube 304)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000986
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Drainage for Station Grounds (Reproduction of 1929 Map), Undated (Map-tube 335)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001129
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; General Diagram for Roof Trusses of Old Machine Shop (Reproduction of 1904 Map), Undated (Map-tube 228)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000475
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Layout of Buildings Proposed Car Repair Yard (Reproduction of 1926 Map), Undated (Map-tube 364)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001084
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Map Showing Close Clearance of Track Along Property of R.B. Safford (Reproduction of 1922 Map), Undated (Map-tube 319)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001028
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Masonry for 3rd Track of South Abutment Bridge 76.28 (Old 54) (Reproduction of 1917 Map), Undated (Map-tube 353)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001004
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Methods of Cross Tie Renewals (Reproduction of 196 Map), Undated (Map-tube 389)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001141
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; North Portion of Shop #7, Car Repair, Undated (Map-tube 230)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000478
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Overhead Clearance of N.Y.S.G. and E. Corp. Wires South of Colliers, NY (Reproduction of 1924 Map), Undated (Map-tube 321)
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Plan for Preframing Deck S.B. and N.B. No. 2 Tracks (Reproduction of 1949 Map), Undated (Map-tube 336)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001006
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Plan for Preframing N.B. and S.B. Tie Decks of Br. 74.15, 1952 (Map-tube 324)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001101
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Plan No. 952 "B", Bridge Number 50, Double Track Half Through Plate Girder, Undated (Map-tube 373)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001019
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Prefabricated Planking To Be Installed at the Passenger Station Platform in Oneonta, NY, 1951 (Map-tube 286)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001133
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Proposed Brackets to Carry Walk on New Turntable (Reproduction of 1924 Map), Undated (Map-tube 311)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001148
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Proposed Connection of East Worcester and Summit Siding to Form Running Track (Reproduction of 1927), Undated (Map-tube 348)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001146
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Proposed Extension of Track for Sheffield Farms and Slawson-Decker Company (Reproduction of 1921 Map), Undated (Map-tube 361)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001122
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Proposed Interlocking Tower and Track Changes in Schenevus, NY (Reproduction of 1922 Map), Undated (Map-tube 351)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001132
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Repairs to Ceiling of Engine House in Oneonta, NY (Reproduction of 1928 Map), Undated (Map-tube 411)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000463
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Steel Plan for South Hill Road Overcrossing, Station 535+42.5 at East Worcester, Schenevus to Richmondville Summit (Reproduction of 1921 Map), Undated (Map-tube 287)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001010
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Track Re-Alignment at Cooperstown Junction (Reproduction of 1920 Map), Undated (Map-tube 367)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001025
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Two Intake Pipes for Standard Oil Company (Reproduction of 1920 Map), Undated (Map-tube 337)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001124
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Undercrossing of South Hill Road Station 267+75, New Line from Schenevus to Richmondville Summit (Reproduction of 1917 Map), Undated (Map-tube 370)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001013
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Undercrossing of South Hill Road Station 267+75, New Line from Schenevus to Richmondville Summit (Reproduction of 1917 Map), Undated (Map-tube 382)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001012
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Yard Track Classification in Binghamton, NY (Reproduction of 1923 Map), Map Number 547, Undated (Flat-file 4)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000872
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Susquehanna Division; Yard Track Classification in Binghamton, NY (Reproduction of 1923 Map with Annotations), Map Number 548, Undated (Flat-file 4)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000872A
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Track Map, Pennsylvania Division Main Line; Green Ridge to Carbondale, Station 1806+92.5 to Station 1859+58.9 (Reproduction of 1945 Map), Undated (Map-tube 493)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001340
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Train Station Evaluations, Undated (Map-tube 225)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000557-BLA000557B
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Typical Sections Through Freight Houses and Freight Yards at Green Island, NY (Reproduction of 1913 Map), Undated (Map-tube 395)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001319; Other Identification Number: 90-24181
  - Delaware and Hudson Corporation: Bevier Street Yard Schematics, Undated (Map-tube 302)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001082
  - Delaware and Hudson Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Bearing Brackets for Bridge 7041, Undated (Map-tube 381)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001017
  - Delaware and Hudson Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Culvert at Station 3514+09 (Reproduction of 1917 Map), Undated (Map-tube 300)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001159
  - Delaware and Hudson Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Masonry Changes to Bridge 70.41 (Old 50) (Reproduction of 1917 Map), Undated (Map-tube 299)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001021
  - Delaware and Hudson Corporation: Susquehanna Division; Proposed Enlargement of Fonda Ave. Yard Office (Reproduction of 1920 Map), Undated (Map-tube 301)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000993
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Company: Floor Plan for Lightweight Passenger Coach (Reproduction of 1937 Map), Undated (Map-tube 276)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001291; Other Identification Number: R-37025
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Company: Susquehanna Division, Details of Boiler Room at Roundhouse in Oneonta, NY, 1942 (Map-tube 439)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000469
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Company: Susquehanna Division, Diesel Inspection Pit Installed on Track No. 3 of Shop #7 in Oneonta, NY (Reproduction of 1954 Map), Undated (Map-tube 266)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000479
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Company: Susquehanna Division; Changes to Interlocking System, Schoharie Junction (Reproduction of 1922 Map), Undated (Map-tube 291)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001128
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Company: Susquehanna Division; Pipe Culvert for Coaling Plant Yard in Delanson, NY (Reproduction of 1927 Map), Undated (Map-tube 292)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001127
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Bootleg Parkway RACO-445-56 (Reproduction of 1951 Map), Undated (Flat-file 3)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000343
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Champlain Division; Hook the Plates Replacing Riveted Plate for No. 9-90" Frog (Reproduction of 1935 Map), Undated (Map-tube 374)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001103
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: CTC "QS" to "GR" Track Changes Vicinity at Union Street in Sidney, NY (Reproduction of 1961), Map Number 477, Undated (Flat-file 477)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000960
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: CTC "QS" to "GR" Track Changes Vicinity in Afton, NY (Reproduction of 1960), Map Number 476, Undated (Flat-file 476)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000959
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Drainage Vicinity of H. Wilty Property in Delanson, NY (Reproduction of 1934 Map), Undated (Map-tube 447)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000488; Other Identification Number: SQ-36-728
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: General Arrangement of Caboose (Reproduction of 1942 Map), Undated (Map-tube 464)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000851
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Highway Crossing Signal Special for Main Street, Granville, NY (Reproduction of 1947 Map), Map Number 541, Undated (Flat-file 3)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000267
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Lettering Cabooses (Reproduction of 1959 Map), Undated (Map-tube 428)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000854
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Lettering Cabooses (Reproduction of 1967 Map), Undated (Map-tube 432)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000849
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Lettering, Baggage Cars (Reproduction of 1967 Map), Undated (Map-tube 243)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001293; Other Identification Numbers: P-41886/7
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Lettering, Coaches (Reproduction of 1967 Map), Undated (Map-tube 252)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001292; Other Identification Number: P-41883
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Lettering, Coaches 201 to 206 Included, 1939 (Map-tube 241)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000846; Other Identification Number: R-37777
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Lettering, Dining Cars (Reproduction of 1967 Map), Undated (Map-tube 244)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001294; Other Identification Numbers: P-41884/5
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Maintenance of Way Building Maxon Road in Schenectady, NY, 1957 (Map-tube 402)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001393
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Land and Tracks of Port Henry, NY (Reproduction of 1957 Map), Map Number 546, Undated (Flat-file 4)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000866